wandtheworld.com 2011-01-06

# Privacy Policy – WandTheWorld.com

**We respect your privacy!**  
Any and all the information collected on this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, disclosed, or loaned!  
Any information you provide will be held with the utmost care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. If you have any questions, please feel free to call or email us.

**Your Personal Information**  
Our site may use forms for information requests and orders including submissions on our blog. Contact information from all forms (including name, email address etc.) is used to deliver requested information to our customers. At no time will we share any of this information with any other person or company.

**Will WandTheWorld.com disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**  
WandTheWorld.com does not sell, trade, rent, or reveal your personal information to others. The only person who will be able to view your email/phone number when you sign up, is the person who referred to to this website. We can also assure you that WandTheWorld.com also does not provide any of your personal information to any other outside party.

**How does WandTheWorld.com protect customer information?**  
When you subscribe to the WandTheWorld.com system we use PayPal as a third-party payment processing server. The secure server software (SSL) at PayPal encrypts all information. We do not collect or see any of this payment information at all. For more information about PayPals privacy policy visit their website.

When you enroll as an Amega Global Business Associate, you will be directed to Amega Global’s payment processing server. The secure server software (SSL) at Amega Global encrypts all information. We do not collect or see any of this payment information at all. For more information about Amega’s privacy policy visit their website at Eamega.com.

**Spam**  
We do not use, nor do we condone the use of unsolicited bulk email. We take this issue very seriously. We do email our customers with order confirmations, and periodically information about product specials, new product announcements, and follow-ups to be sure you are satisfied with your purchase. If you do not wish to receive any email from us at all, you can click the “unsubscribe” link, or simply send us a short note and we will not send you any correspondence. We sincerely appreciate you visiting our site, and hope that you return often.
